<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[philippeschaedler]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[philippeschaedler]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/philippeschaedler/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 22:31:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/philippeschaedler/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Education I discovered early on that education is the key to being a successful and happy hairstylist. Continuing education is what makes our industry so much fun because it promotes creativity and passion. Education has always been a big part of my work as a hairstylist, starting back in Europe when I was still in my teens and continuing to this day. Just as in other professions, attending seminars to learn the latest developments in their fields, the best hair stylists also take advantage of classes and workshops to learn and become familiar with the latest products and techniques. I have taken advanced classes with the Toni&Guy Academy every few months for many years. From precision haircutting to color correction to the latest trends in styling and hair care, I love it all! I find it exciting to be presented with the latest discoveries, which I can then bring back to you, the client, with the utmost confidence.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.philippeschaedler.com/Education.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6a2fa612-ec5e-4e72-8872-2722b3c43451</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 22:31:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[philippeschaedler.com]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>philippeschaedler.com</h1><p>Philippe Schaedler</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/e10c24cf-6acc-4013-ab91-c8c3cbac9472.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/philippeschaedler/philippeschaedlercom/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6fd6aa32-a390-4889-84c0-84a4ab0dce6b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 22:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for dropping by... If you’re looking for a Santa Monica hair stylist who offers high quality and personal service, you’ve come to the right place. You will receive the attention and personal service you’ll come to expect and enjoy. I offer many years of experience in consultation, Toni&Guy and Vidal Sassoon hair cutting techniques, as well as hair coloring, and I thrive on continuing education. I have extensive training with the use of Goldwell and TIGI permanent and semi-permanent haircoloring products. With these excellent color lines, I can provide the best and most vibrant hair coloring for my clients. I am also a certified and experienced Brazilian Blowout Specialist. To learn more about the Brazilian Blowout treatment, click here.  I have also been trained in the Japanese Straightening treatment and have been offering the service for more than eight years. If you have any questions about my services, feel free to contact me via email and I will get back to you as soon as possible. Please visit me at Salon Tosca, a Santa Monica hair salon on 3014 Wilshire Boulevard. Let me put my education and experience to work for you!  Salon Tosca 3014 Wilshire Blvd.  Santa Monica, CA 90403 Brazilian Blow Out Certified Stylist Clients Comments   Now Offering the  HYBRID Japanese/Brazilian Treatment The Hybridtext                      Tuesdays: Phenix Salon Suites 13455 Maxella Ave  Marina del Rey, CA 90292</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.philippeschaedler.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">086b59c7-e4a9-4be5-9dbb-f027539501a3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 20:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Services & Prices]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Services & Prices</h1><p>Haircut 105 / (wet & dry cut - blow dry included)Extra long, dense hair 125 (wet & dry cut - blow dry included) Barbering (men's) 70 Shampoo & Styling 50 to 60</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/philippeschaedler/services-and-prices/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f6ff8a93-5216-4581-ad7a-59ee18b26206</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 20:04:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>